sup everyone came as a thief a fee with
a very special video today now as you
all know yesterday was Christmas or as I
like to call it another game which
soccer has returned yet
you know what I mean but that's
ok as you know me and I'm gonna remix
are coming on some day so it's all good
and now since the death of Christmas I
thought damn I'll do another
Christmas heart because I know how much
you love that because I did last
year and I thought hey maybe I'll just
make some of these of little bit
jealous never that I further adieu here
we go now first off my mama my mama she
got she got me two of these I
don't know I don't know why she got two
of them but as you all know our
lifestyle was I mean she told me they
were about 10 bucks I guess you got two
of them cuz they were in the bargain bin
or some I mean but yeah
a dog she said you know 10 bucks
each these want a dog look at that these
were a dollar mama
you you I don't
I want a good bit oh I'll
show you some good she got me too
soft come on DVDs as you know dr. box
event harm this is falling down
well I'll put them right there oh yeah
as you can see she got me to suck on
DVDs dr. Hawks revenge and ready I'm
Sonic as you all know duck on to avenge
is like my all-time favorite sock on the
ground DVD and
you just can't top it it sucks 70
minutes of fun and some now another
movie she got me was was Batman Forever
cuz this is my favorite Batman movie I
mean I don't offer watching on VHS cuz I
don't even got a VHS of some so so
she screwed up
she also got me some popcorn I'm moving
that I mean clearly she got it from some
goodwill some because it's like
table over the box so yeah this isn't
going be some collectors isn't damn
I can't get this open let's Peter
Pan what the what the I got talked
to my mom about that someone's
getting their ass beat
I know it's my mama or if it's let's do
that good wa ba
that
where we gonna mop or now I mean did you
know what's sad too
this was really something moving that
super huge moving that she bought me a
flash shirt she keep on pawpaw she even
bought me this she she even bought me
this fast or that did you go back oh it
does this because we just got we just
watched the Justice League and
so she thought here take this what's the
damn she she also got me this
this hacky sack ball
I mean Canada represent him
mama I'm from Canada I am from
America America bed did awesome some
crusty Brown which I don't know
what if he might be all I know I I
don't give a is oh my
God damn you